### **Abraham John**

Born 31st of August 2000 • jabrahamjohns@yahoo.com • +254793329255

#### INTRO

#### **SUMMARY**

An adaptable student with the knowhow of application development, programming skills and database management not forgetting scheduling, organization and client and good customer service experience.

I am to leverage y skills to fill the vacancy at your company. Frequently praised for good communication dependability hard work and reliable to achieve set goals both individually and group settings

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Virtual and sales assistant

Freelance • Aug 2022 - Present

Swansea shop and wholesales

Work as time to time part-time VA and assistant at the stores to manage emails, social media and delivery of goods.

#### Sales and marketing intern

Direct and perfect international • Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

Direct and perfect international, Mombasa

This position was an internship, and my tasks included

- \* Promotion of goods and products
- \* Sales and marketing of fast moving products

Skills and accomplishment include:

- \* Completion of training
- \* Sales skills and customer experience management

# Web designer and virtual assistant

AJ networks • Jan 2022 - Present

AJ networks, Kenya

Am currently working as a freelancer and an intern on a part-time basis.

And my tasks and responsibilities include:

- \* Maintaining a well-organized digital filing system and backups to reduce data loss.
- \* Developing custom websites to meet clients' needs
- \* Collaboration with web content editors to facilitate website maintenance
- \* Mail and booking management for clients

#### **Events security guard**

Wild waters • Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

Wild waters, Mombasa

Was a part-time security events guard job aimed at impacting customer skills and service offering

- \* Accuracy skills and time management
- \* Attention to details whether large or small which is essential in every working details
- \* Time management

## Packager and delivery

Packaging • Nov 2020 - Jan 2021

Moffataste cakes and pastry

Worked in the nightshift packaging department.

- \* Packaging skills
- \* Organization
- \* Attention to detail.

## sales boy and assistant

Pakawa general stores • Jan 2020 - Oct 2020

provided by the company

- \* Keep store records
- \* Deliver goods to customer on order
- \* Update and keep track of stocks
- \* Unload goods at specific intervals when in place to do so \*
- \* Cleaning and safety handling

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **VIRTUAL ASSISTANT ALX**

University Africa • Jan 2022 - Aug 2022

#### **BSC MATHEMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE**

Technical university of Mombasa • Sep 2019 - Jul 2024

# A-LEVEL DEGREE, limyounsim good

people mission school • Feb 2016 - Nov 2019

# **O-LEVEL DEGREE**

St.patricks Neema Academy • Jan 2009 - Nov 2015

### SKILLS

Operating systems Linux IT equipment installation and configuration IT training IT support

Github (or other software version management systems) Database query languages (SQL, others)

Computer, laptop maintenance and repair Code documentation CSS Bootstrap C, C# or C++ Artificial intelligence (AI)

Application programming interfaces (API) Social media usage (Facebook, Twitter, etc.) Office tools: Word, Excel, Outlook HTML

Installing new software E-mail and internet Communication Customer service Customer support, CRM systems

Basic computer maintenance

# CERTIFICATES

### **Certified Secretary (CS)**

• Aug 2022

#### LANGUAGES

#### Swahili

Spoken: Basic • Written: Basic

**English** 

Spoken: Fluent • Written: Fluent

### **ASSOCIATIONS**

### **Crossroads fellowship**

**Humanitarian Volunteer** 

#### Redcross

IT and humanitarian Volunteer

### HOBBIES

learning Travelling Watching Martial arts Swimming Coding Driving HOBBIES.

### LINKS

https://ajnets.netlify.app/

www.github.com/jabrahamjohn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jabrahamjohns

#### REFERENCES

# Nelly kariuki • Co-founder, pakawa general stores

Manager • +254 723264041 • nellywanjiru@gmail.com

# Meshark lodenyi • Founder, Swansea stores

• +254 724267843 • mesharklodenyi@gmail.com

# Mathematics masai • Security head, wild waters kenya

• +254 728343987 • muthama@gmail.com